let questions = [
    {
        question_number: 1,
        question: "Who is the most decorated Olympian of all time, with the highest number of Olympic ",
        choices: ["Usain Bolt", "Michael Phelps", "Simone Biles", "Carl Lewis"],
        correctAnswer: 1 // Index 1 corresponds to the correct choice "Michael Phelps"
    },
    {
        question_number: 2,
        question: "Which football club won the UEFA Champions League in 2021?",
        choices: ["Bayern Munich", "Manchester City", "Real Madrid", "Chelsea"],
        correctAnswer: 3 // Index 3 corresponds to the correct choice "Real Madrid"
    },
    {
        question_number: 3,
        question: "In which sport do competitors try to hit a shuttlecock over a net using rackets?",
        choices: ["Badminton", "Squash", "Table Tennis", "Tennis"],
        correctAnswer: 0 // Index 0 corresponds to the correct choice "Badminton"
    },
    {
        question_number: 4,
        question: "Which athlete is known as 'The Greatest' in the sport of boxing?",
        choices: ["Muhammad Ali", "Mike Tyson", "Sugar Ray Robinson", "Floyd Mayweather Jr."],
        correctAnswer: 0 // Index 0 corresponds to the correct choice "Muhammad Ali"
    },
    {
        question_number: 5,
        question: "Which country has won the most gold medals in the history of the Winter Olympics?",
        choices: ["United States", "Norway", "Russia", "Germany"],
        correctAnswer: 1 // Index 1 corresponds to the correct choice "Norway"
    },
    {
        question_number: 6,
        question: "In which city did the 2016 Summer Olympics take place?",
        choices: ["Rio de Janeiro", "London", "Beijing", "Sydney"],
        correctAnswer: 0 // Index 0 corresponds to the correct choice "Rio de Janeiro"
    },
    {
        question_number: 7,
        question: "Which golfer has the most major championship wins in history?",
        choices: ["Tiger Woods", "Jack Nicklaus", "Arnold Palmer", "Phil Mickelson"],
        correctAnswer: 1 // Index 1 corresponds to the correct choice "Jack Nicklaus"
    },
    {
        question_number: 8,
        question: "Which sport is associated with the Stanley Cup?",
        choices: ["Ice Hockey", "Basketball", "American Football", "Baseball"],
        correctAnswer: 0 // Index 0 corresponds to the correct choice "Ice Hockey"
    },
    {
        question_number: 9,
        question: "Which country has won the most Women's World Cup titles in football (soccer)?",
        choices: ["United States", "Brazil", "Germany", "Norway"],
        correctAnswer: 0 // Index 0 corresponds to the correct choice "United States"
    },
    {
        question_number: 10,
        question: "Who won the NBA MVP (Most Valuable Player) award for the 2020-2021 season?",
        choices: ["LeBron James", "Giannis Antetokounmpo", "Kevin Durant", "Nikola Jokić"],
        correctAnswer: 3 // Index 3 corresponds to the correct choice "Nikola Jokić"
    }
];